A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, photographs, RG 2, 1958-1990 FA499
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, photographs, RG 2, 1958-1990
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA499
5.42 Cubic Feet 11 legal document boxes, and 1 half-legal document box
Scope and Contents
Comprised of photographs separated from the paper collection at the time of micfofilming.
Separated Materials
All contents were separated from the paper collection during the process of reformatting to microfilm.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure, similar to the structure found in the Project files.
Photographs
- International, 100; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - (A-C), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brewbaker, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Colton, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Corey, R. B., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gasbarre, Louis C., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Halstead, Scott B. (Meetings), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Harrington, J. B., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Herdt, Robert W., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hopkins, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ingles, Thelma, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Knowles, John H., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Leitzman, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lyman, R.W., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - McKelvey, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ohlson, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rachie, K. O., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Segal, S. J., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Holland), 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Kemp, Graham H.), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Olson), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Sawyer), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Sturrock), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Uptham), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Telford Work (Europe), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Unesco (A-U), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - United Nations World Health Organization (A-C), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Uykaukalova, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Administration - Applications for Employment, 101; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Applications for Employment - Agricultural Programs, 101.01
    Agriculture
    - Abdullahi, A. M. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- International Organizations, 103; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Hospital San Pedro (Necha Guatemala), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - International Institute for Sorghum and Millet, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Schools (Silva), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Greater Voice for Africa in the United States (Africa Policy Watch Project), 121; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Armitage Ballet, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Theatre for the Blind, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- United States, 200; 2.35 Cubic Feet 5 legal document boxes
  United States
  - United States - General, 200
    - Academy of Judaic, Christian, and Islamic Studies, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Actors Theatre of Louisville, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - American Ballet Comedies, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - American Center for Students and Artists, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - American Conservatory (Supplementary Material), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Am-Aq, 1958-1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Andean Foundation (Rural Development), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Anthropoid Research Foundation, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Atlanta Municipal Theatre, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Bearden Contemporary Dance Theatre, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Birmingham - Southern College Theatre, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Bo - Bu, 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Brewster, D., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Ca - Center for Arts, 1963-1985 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Center for the Biology (Natural Science), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Center for Media Studies, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Center for New American Media (Kolker), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Central Area Motivation Program, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Chandler, R. F., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Chia, J. T., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Children's Theatre Company and School, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Cincinnati Ballet Company, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - City Street Theatre Ensemble, Inc., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Cl - Cu, 1961-1986 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Cobey, H. T., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Colorado State University (Tissue Culture for Crops) (Hall) (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Concept East Theatre, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Da - Di, 1958-1978 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Dallas Theatre Center, Inc., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Darlington, L. C., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Dartmouth College Hopkins Center, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Dunlea, J. V. -(du Pont Spangler), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Eden and Associates, Environmental Concerns, Inc., 1964; 1975 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Fa - Fl, 1958-1980 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Firehouse Theatre, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - First Presbyterian Church (Wright), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Flaherty, W., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Florida Bird Survey, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Fort Wayne Fine Arts Foundation, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Franklin Institute Research Laboratories (Solid Waste Separators), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Gard, Robert, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Ge - Gr, 1955-1985 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Georgia Mountains Planning and Development Commission, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Germantown Laboratories (Grosse), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Goodwill Industries, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Gorden-Canwell Theological Society, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Gottsegen, I., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Gretna City Council (Rural Development), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Guild of Performing Arts, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Harvard University Education, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Helicon Foundation, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Henning Company, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - House, Leland R., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Ho - Hu, 1966-1977 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Independent Film and Video Distribution Center, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Institute of the Americas - Institute for the Arts and Urban Resources, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Interarts, Inc. (Colyer), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Iowa State University (Browning), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Ithaca College Music, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - King, F. P., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Japan U.S. Friendship Commission, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Jenkins Dance Company, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Lake Placid Club, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Landress, P. G., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - League of American Wheelman, Inc., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Le - Li, 1964-1978 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Louisville Philharmonic Society, Inc., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Lucas, R. A., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Lutheran Medical Center (Health Education Institute), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Mackinal Environmental Research and Educational Institute, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Maryknoll Fathers, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Schmitt), 1958 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Mayberry, V. R., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Mayfield High School Arts, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Michigan State University, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Midland - Odessa Symphony Orchestra, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Mi - Mo, 1964; 1971 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Muhlerberg College, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Napoli, C., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Natasha and Tamara Dance, Inc., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - National Center for Atmospheric Research, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - National Educational Television and Radio Center, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - National Center for Exp. in Television (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - National Institute of Health (Krause), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - National Medical Association Foundation, Inc., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Nelson, N., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Ne - No, 1969-1977 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Northwestern University (Music), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Northwestern University Library, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Ohio State University, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Oregon State College (Henderson), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Orme School and Orton, T., 1971; 1978 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Paarlberg, Don (Agricultural Economist Economic Advisor to the President), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Pan American Sanitary Bureau, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Pendleton, R. L., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Penland School of Crafts (Supplementary Material), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Pennsylvania Ballet, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Pennsylvania Community Services, Inc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - People's Light and Theatre Company, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Petereson, J. B. (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Ph - Per, 1965-1978 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Project Awareness Teenage Pregnancy, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Company, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Ramell, G. C., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Ravenholt, A., 1990 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Reice, M., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Reining, P. C., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Reynolds Aluminum International Services, Inc., 1984 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Rizk, J, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Robertson, L. D., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Rockefeller University (Lynch), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Rubin, S., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Rutgers University (Zimmerlli Museum), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Sagay, Orlando J., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - St. Mary's College, Minnesota, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - St. Paul Council of Arts and Science, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Salter, L., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - San Fernando Valley State College (Bland), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - San Francisco Performing Arts Center, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - San Francisco Art Institute, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Sarah Lawrence College (Performing Arts Center), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Scientific American, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Scholarship, Education, and Defense Fund for Racial Equality, Inc., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Sioux City Foundation, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Smalls, H.M., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Smith, Geddeth, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Smithsonian Institute for Traveling Exhibit Service (LOAR), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Stage South, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Stanford University (Shaw), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - State University of New York at Albany (Bight Atlas), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo (Rottenberg), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Sp - Su, 1967-1978 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - TAP - Arts and Crafts, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Taylor, H., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Tempkin, M., 1984 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Theatre Atlanta, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Tuskegee Institute, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Tuskegee Institute (Slides), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 178A)
    - United Nations Association of the U.S.A. (Jackson), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - U.S. Agency for International Development, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - U.S. Agriculture, 1958-1982 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - U.S. Brooklyn, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - U.S. Civil Administration of the Ryukyu Island Mukaida, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - U.S. - State (Bacon), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - United States Aid - (Samuel Cameron Litzenberger), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - United States Interior Indian Affairs, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - University of Alaska Geographical Institute (Supplementary Material), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - University of California (Comfrey), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - University of California (B - S), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - University of Connecticut, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - University of Florida (Aldrich), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - University of Georgia (Himel), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - University of Illinois (Krannet Center), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - University of Maryland (Visual Arts), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - University of Massachusetts (Wyckoff), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - University of Michigan (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - University of Pennsylvania (Chemistry and Biology), 1958; 1971 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - University of Rhode Island (Greus Wagon Theatre), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - University of Wisconsin (International Agricultural Program), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Vagabond Marionettes, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Drama), 1958-1966 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Wake Forest University Art Center (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Walters, J. B., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Webster College Performing Arts, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Weisburg, Roger, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Wi - Wh, 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Wolf, M. R., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Wolf Trap Farm Park (Filene Center), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Wood, P., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Woodlands Institute (Taylor - Ide), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - WNET - Thirteen, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Writght, Edward V., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Yuriko and Dance Co., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - YMCA (University of Illinois), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - United States - Medical Sciences, 200A
    Medical sciences
    - Baylor University (Medical School), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - University of Miami (Medical School), 1958 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - University of Minnesota, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 200E
    Fellowships
    - Beasley, J., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Currier, T. C., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Haines, J. M., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Waugh, Lawrence J., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - United States - Declinations, 200F
    - George Williams College, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - United States - Humanities and Arts, 200R
    Humanities
    - Roundabout Theatre Co., Inc., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Gatmaiton, Antonio P., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - Palafox, L. A., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - Pineda, D. P., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - University of the Philippines (Romulo), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 232)
- Philippines, 242; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Philippines
  - Philippines - General, 242
    - University of Texas (Medical School), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Vanderbilt University (Medical School), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 242D
    Science; Agriculture
    - Paterno, E. S., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 242E
    - Abilay, Teodoro, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - Asuncian, D. R. (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - Atienza, Z., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - Barrera, R. M. M., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - Bendana, Nelia, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Cejalvo, F. V., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Domingo, E. A., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - Janolino, V. G., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Kole, E. M., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Ona, Purificacion L., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Recto, Aida E., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Ramin, B. B., 1967; 1969 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Ventura, M. V. P., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Philippines - Declinations, 242F
    - Philippine Normal College, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 247)
- Internship Program - Minority School Superintendents, 260; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Canidates (Rodriguez, L. P.), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Mickens, C. E., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - University of Texas (Photographic and Oral History Project), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 250)
- Playwrights in Residence, 272; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Chin, F. C., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Harris, T., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Kreil Kamp, B., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Stowell, J., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Yamauchi, W., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 255)
- Latin America, 300; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Latin America
  - Latin America - General, 300
    - Instituto de Nutrition de Centro America y Panama (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - Pan American Health Service, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Latin America - Medical Sceinces, 300A
    - Pan American Federation of Medical Schools, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 258)
- Argentina, 301; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Argentina
  - Catholic University Buenos Aires, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 259)
- Brazil, 305; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Brazil
  - Brazil - General, 305
    - Puricelli, C. A., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Cabral, V. R., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Dias, M., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Guama Ecological Research Area (Dias), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Neto, Calasans, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - University of Minas Gerias - Veternary Medicine - A-L, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - University of Rio Grande (Biochemistry - Microbiology), 1958 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Rural University of Rio Grande du Sol, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 305E
    - Balmer, E., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Campos, A. E., Campos, M.S., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Ferreira, F. I., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Medeiras, M. C., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Meira, A. L. (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Ometto, D. A., 1961 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Reis, Jose Ovorio, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Ribeiro, J. P., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Rodrigues, D. D., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - University of Brasil (Physiology), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Wagner, E., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 279)
- Bolivia, 303; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Bolivia
  - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 303E
    - Ramirez, R. R., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 261)
- Chile, 309; 0.94 Cubic Feet 2 legal document boxes
  Chile
  - Chile - General, 309
    - University of Chile (Inta), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - University of Concepcion (Library), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - Chile - Medical Sciences, 309A
    - University of Concepcion (Supplementary Material), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 309D
    Agriculture; Science
    - Chile National Science and Agriculture, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 309E
    - Balmaceda, J. P., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Canos C., Raul, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Madrid, Emilio, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Ossandon, Edgardo, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 287)
- Colombia, 311; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Colombia
  - Colombia - General, 311
    - Barrosa, G., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Jaimes Capacho, L. R., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Neurological Institute of Colombia (Ca - Pa), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Gonzalez, A., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Ternent, J. A. S., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - Universidad del Valle (Gomez-Osorio), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 311D
    - Colombian Agricultural Report, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 311E
    - Alvarez R., J. A. (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Arango, N. L., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - Ariza Pardo, Uriel, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - Ca - Pe, 1959-1969 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Owen-Bartlett, E. J., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Rangel P., D. J., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Ricuarte, Maria - Rivera, Antonio, 1966; 1972 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Zuluagar, F. U., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 302)
- Costa Rica, 313; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Costa Rica
  - Costa Rica (Box 7, Folder 303)
- Ecuador, 317; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Ecuador
  - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 317E
    - Alava, A. M. - Arevalo N., M. A., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Ca - Cl, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Diaz C. G., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Estrella E., W. R., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Estupinan R., E. A., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Guzman V., G. G., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Larrea Horrera, P. E., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Luzurlanga, F. G., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Manosalvas, L., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Me - Or, 1959-1969 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Sanchez, P. J., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Suarez C., C., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - Viteri Silva, J. E., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 316)
- Guatemala, 319; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Guatemala
  - Guatemala - General, 319
    - Gonzalez A., Danilo, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Pacheco, J. G., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 319D
    - Schieber, Eugenio, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Guatemala - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 319E
    - Castillo de Leon, L. M., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - Villagram, Crespo, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 321)
- Honduras, 321; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Honduras
  - Escuela Agricola Panamericana, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 322)
  - Silva G., A. R. (Box 7, Folder 323)
- Mexico, 323; 0.94 Cubic Feet 2 legal document boxes
  Mexico
  - Mexico - General, 323
    - Amiera, Diana Cecelia Ortega, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - Carrielo Liz, A., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - Escuela Normal del Estado, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - Guadalajara Autonomous Universidad, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - Guadalajara Autonomous University, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - La Campana Experiment Station (Chihuahua), 1978 (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - Munoz, F. I. - Pena, R. J., 1965; 1977 (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - National Corn Commission (Alvarez y Luna), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - National Polytechnic Institute (Rosenblueth), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - National School of Agriculture (Library), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - Rice - Wray, E., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - Rubio del Cueto, A., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - Sabido, Miguel, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - Villarreal Guzman, R., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 323E
    - Acosta S., R., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - Aguilar Yepez, Samuel, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - Arzac, Washington Ulpiano, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - Baca, C. G. A., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - Ba - Co, 1965-1982 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - Chapa Romo, M.T., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 342A)
    - Covarrubias C., R., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 342B)
    - Garcia H., F., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 343)